(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Frank's cousins were coming to town.
He was excited.
This was the first time he would see
them in person.
His cousins lived in another country.
He never saw them.
The only time he saw them was when
he webbed Cam with them.
He also talked on the phone with them.
Frank was excited to have someone his age
to talk to.
Frank got all his video games ready.
He could not wait to play with them.
His cousins came.
They hugged and laughed.
Frank told them stories about his country.
They told him stories about their country.
They played games.
Then they ate dinner.
After dinner, they continued to play games.